https://www.designlinkarchitecture.com/online-privacy-policy/

close
Schedule FREE 1 Hour ConsultationPrivacy PolicyGive DesignLink Architecture & Planning a Call Today!(480) 607-0096
Online Privacy Policy
DesignLink Architecture & Planning, (), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with DesignLink Architecture & Planning of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to DesignLink Architecture & Planning [BF1], and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of http://www.designlinkarchitecture.com/ [BF2] you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.
We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected
DesignLink Architecture & Planning may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from http://www.designlinkarchitecture.com/  . DesignLink Architecture & Planning [BF18]  may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
DesignLink Architecture & Planning does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.
DesignLink Architecture & Planning may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.
DesignLink Architecture & Planning may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon DesignLink Architecture & Planning and/or our website;Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of DesignLink Architecture & Planning; andPerform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of http://www.designlinkarchitecture.com/ and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
DesignLink Architecture & Planning does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to admin@designlinkarchitecture.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. DesignLink Architecture & Planning does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
DesignLink Architecture & Planning shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
DesignLink Architecture & Planning reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at http://www.designlinkarchitecture.com/, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time DesignLink Architecture & Planning decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: admin@designlinkarchitecture.com
Telephone Number:  480 607 0096
Mailing Address:
DesignLink Architecture & Planning14415 N 73rd St #109Scottsdale, Arizona 85260
10/01/2016
No ACF gallery field data foundProjects
Our TeamDebra WeisbergDebra Weisberg is a licensed architect and a founding partner of DesignLink architecture. As such, she played a decisive role the development of the firm’s philosophy of personalized design approach and team participation. Read more about Debra Weisberg.Julia NovoaJulia is a Senior project Manager and registered architect in Arizona. As part of Designlink for 28 years, she is responsible for Construction Documentation. Her attention to detail and immense experience, make her a key component of the Designlink Team.Schedule a Free 1 Hour Consultation at Our Office in ScottsdaleCall Us today at(480) 607-0096Full NameEmail *PhoneLocation of ProjectHow Can We Help?Submit DesignLink Architecture & Planning14415 North 73rd Street #109Scottsdale, Arizona 85260(480) 607-0096View Larger Map / Get DirectionsVoted Best of Houzz 2020!National Kitchen & Bath Association© 2020 DesignLink Architecture & PlanningPrivacy Policy
closemap-markerchevron-downphonebars
linkedin
facebook
pinterest
youtube
rss
twitter
instagram
